{
  "airplanes": {
    "root": "AIRPLANES",
    "cancel": "AIRPLANES_CANCEL",
    "createError": "AIRPLANES_CREATE_ERROR",
    "createPrompt": "AIRPLANES_CREATE_PROMPT",
    "createRequest": "AIRPLANES_CREATE_REQUEST",
    "createResponse": "AIRPLANES_CREATE_RESPONSE",
    "delete": "AIRPLANES_DELETE",
    "deleteError": "AIRPLANES_DELETE_ERROR",
    "deletePrompt": "AIRPLANES_DELETE_PROMPT",
    "deleteRequest": "AIRPLANES_DELETE_REQUEST",
    "deleteResponse": "AIRPLANES_DELETE_RESPONSE",
    "edit": "AIRPLANES_EDIT",
    "editError": "AIRPLANES_EDIT_ERROR",
    "editPrompt": "AIRPLANES_EDIT_PROMPT",
    "editRequest": "AIRPLANES_EDIT_REQUEST",
    "editResponse": "AIRPLANES_EDIT_RESPONSE",
    "error": "AIRPLANES_ERROR",
    "request": "AIRPLANES_REQUEST",
    "response": "AIRPLANES_RESPONSE",
    "searchResultsPage": "AIRPLANES_SEARCH_RESULTS_PAGE",
    "searchResultsPerPage": "AIRPLANES_SEARCH_RESULTS_PER_PAGE"
  },

  "airports": {
    "root": "AIRPORTS",
    "cancel": "AIRPORTS_CANCEL",
    "createError": "AIRPORTS_CREATE_ERROR",
    "createPrompt": "AIRPORTS_CREATE_PROMPT",
    "createRequest": "AIRPORTS_CREATE_REQUEST",
    "createResponse": "AIRPORTS_CREATE_RESPONSE",
    "delete": "AIRPORTS_DELETE",
    "deleteError": "AIRPORTS_DELETE_ERROR",
    "deletePrompt": "AIRPORTS_DELETE_PROMPT",
    "deleteRequest": "AIRPORTS_DELETE_REQUEST",
    "deleteResponse": "AIRPORTS_DELETE_RESPONSE",
    "edit": "AIRPORTS_EDIT",
    "editError": "AIRPORTS_EDIT_ERROR",
    "editPrompt": "AIRPORTS_EDIT_PROMPT",
    "editRequest": "AIRPORTS_EDIT_REQUEST",
    "editResponse": "AIRPORTS_EDIT_RESPONSE",
    "error": "AIRPORTS_ERROR",
    "request": "AIRPORTS_REQUEST",
    "response": "AIRPORTS_RESPONSE",
    "searchResultsPage": "AIRPORTS_SEARCH_RESULTS_PAGE",
    "searchResultsPerPage": "AIRPORTS_SEARCH_RESULTS_PER_PAGE"
  },
  
  "authentication": {
    "root": "AUTHENTICATION",
    "cancel": "AUTHENTICATION_CANCEL",
    "createAccountError": "AUTHENTICATION_CREATE_ACCOUNT_ERROR",
    "createAccountRequest": "AUTHENTICATION_CREATE_ACCOUNT_REQUEST",
    "createAccountSuccess": "AUTHENTICATION_CREATE_ACCOUNT_SUCCESS",
    "error": "AUTHENTICATION_ERROR",
    "forgotPasswordError": "AUTHENTICATION_FORGOT_PASSWORD_ERROR",
    "forgotPasswordRequest": "AUTHENTICATION_FORGOT_PASSWORD_REQUEST",
    "forgotPasswordSuccess": "AUTHENTICATION_FORGOT_PASSWORD_SUCCESS",
    "loginError": "AUTHENTICATION_LOGIN_ERROR",
    "loginRequest": "AUTHENTICATION_LOGIN_REQUEST",
    "loginSuccess": "AUTHENTICATION_LOGIN_SUCCESS",
    "logout": "AUTHENTICATION_LOGOUT",
    "prompt": "AUTHENTICATION_PROMPT"
  },

  "bookings": {
    "root": "BOOKINGS",
    "cancel": "BOOKINGS_CANCEL",
    "create": "BOOKINGS_CREATE",
    "createError": "BOOKINGS_CREATE_ERROR",
    "createPrompt": "BOOKINGS_CREATE_PROMPT",
    "createRequest": "BOOKINGS_CREATE_REQUEST",
    "createResponse": "BOOKINGS_CREATE_RESPONSE",
    "delete": "BOOKINGS_DELETE",
    "deleteError": "BOOKINGS_DELETE_ERROR",
    "deletePrompt": "BOOKINGS_DELETE_PROMPT",
    "deleteRequest": "BOOKINGS_DELETE_REQUEST",
    "deleteResponse": "BOOKINGS_DELETE_RESPONSE",
    "edit": "BOOKINGS_EDIT",
    "editError": "BOOKINGS_EDIT_ERROR",
    "editPrompt": "BOOKINGS_EDIT_PROMPT",
    "editRequest": "BOOKINGS_EDIT_REQUEST",
    "editResponse": "BOOKINGS_EDIT_RESPONSE",
    "error": "BOOKINGS_ERROR",
    "request": "BOOKINGS_REQUEST",
    "reset": "BOOKINGS_RESET",
    "response": "BOOKINGS_RESPONSE",
    "searchError": "BOOKINGS_SEARCH_ERROR",
    "searchResultsPage": "BOOKINGS_SEARCH_RESULTS_PAGE",
    "searchResultsPerPage": "BOOKINGS_SEARCH_RESULTS_PER_PAGE",
    "select": "BOOKINGS_SELECT"
  },

  "flights": {
    "root": "FLIGHTS",
    "cancel": "FLIGHTS_CANCEL",
    "createError": "FLIGHTS_CREATE_ERROR",
    "createPrompt": "FLIGHTS_CREATE_PROMPT",
    "createRequest": "FLIGHTS_CREATE_REQUEST",
    "createResponse": "FLIGHTS_CREATE_RESPONSE",
    "delete": "FLIGHTS_DELETE",
    "deleteError": "FLIGHTS_DELETE_ERROR",
    "deletePrompt": "FLIGHTS_DELETE_PROMPT",
    "deleteRequest": "FLIGHTS_DELETE_REQUEST",
    "deleteResponse": "FLIGHTS_DELETE_RESPONSE",
    "edit": "FLIGHTS_EDIT",
    "editError": "FLIGHTS_EDIT_ERROR",
    "editPrompt": "FLIGHTS_EDIT_PROMPT",
    "editRequest": "FLIGHTS_EDIT_REQUEST",
    "editResponse": "FLIGHTS_EDIT_RESPONSE",
    "error": "FLIGHTS_ERROR",
    "request": "FLIGHTS_REQUEST",
    "requestReturn": "FLIGHTS_REQUEST_RETURN",
    "returnFlightResponse": "FLIGHTS_RETURN_RESPONSE",
    "response": "FLIGHTS_RESPONSE",
    "searchRequest": "FLIGHTS_SEARCH_REQUEST",
    "searchResponse": "FLIGHTS_SEARCH_RESPONSE"
  },

  "httpRequest": {
    "delete": "DELETE",
    "get": "GET",
    "post": "POST",
    "put": "PUT"
  },

  "orchestration": {
    "root": "ORCHESTRATION",
    "contentNegotiation": "ORCHESTRATION_CONTENTNEGOTIATION",
    "error": "ORCHESTRATION_ERROR",
    "ready": "ORCHESTRATION_READY",
    "services": "ORCHESTRATION_SERVICES",
    "start": "ORCHESTRATION_START",
    "stop": "ORCHESTRATION_STOP"
  },

  "payments": {
    "root": "PAYMENTS",
    "error": "PAYMENTS_ERROR",
    "request": "PAYMENTS_REQUEST",
    "response": "PAYMENTS_RESPONSE"
  },

  "routes": {
    "root": "ROUTES",
    "error": "ROUTES_ERROR",
    "request": "ROUTES_REQUEST",
    "response": "ROUTES_RESPONSE"
  },

  "users": {
    "root": "USERS",
    "error": "USERS_ERROR",
    "request": "USERS_REQUEST",
    "response": "USERS_RESPONSE"
  }
}